altayyaronline.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | Altayyar Online

At Altayyaronline.com we respect your need to understand how your personal information is dealt with. We have set out this Privacy Policy to familiarize you with our practices and demonstrate our commitment to your privacy. We may change the content of this website at any time whenever it deems appropriate and necessary in our opinion without prior notice and consequently our privacy policy may change at any time in the future. You agree to revisit the privacy policy page regularly and your continued access to or use of the website will mean that you agree to the changes.

Altayyaronline.com is owned and registered by Altayyar Travel Group for travel and tourism, Riyadh, Saudi Arabia., Altayyaronline.com also comprises of the mobile site, Smartphone App Platforms such as iOS, Android, Windows (all together referred to as “Site”). This privacy policy does not apply to the websites of our business partners, corporate affiliates or to any other third parties, even if their websites are linked to the site. We recommend you to review the respective privacy statements of the other parties with whom you interact. 

By browsing, visiting, accessing and/or using the services on this Site (or searching for any of the pages on this Site), the customer (“You”) explicitly consents and agrees to our Privacy Policy laid out herein. You also agree that the information furnished by you is lawful, true and correct and does not violate or infringe any laws. In case of any violations, infringement, furnishing of wrongful or unauthorized information, Altayyaronline.com or Altayyar Travel Group shall not be liable for the same. 

### Information we collect, collate and/or use

On you are accessing of this Site, certain information about you, such as: 

#### Personal, Booking & Transactional Information

Personal information means data that can be used to identify any individual such as name, address, mailing address, telephone number, e - mail address, credit card number, cardholder name, expiration date, information about the travel, bookings, bookings, co-passengers, travel preferences and all details that may be requested while any customers visits or uses the website or Site 

You provide us information about yourself while using or visiting site or if you register for an account with the Service or logon, including by connecting with the Service via a third-party service, or by “following,” “becoming a fan,” adding the Altayyaronline application, etc., on a third party website or network 

#### Other information 

When you browse through the website, we may collect information regarding the domain and host from which you access the Internet for operational and security purposes, the Internet Protocol address of the computer or Internet Service Provider you are using, and anonymous website statistical data. The Website uses cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Personal Information will not be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. We use first party cookie and third party cookie for better targeting and tracking purpose. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties 

You may be asked for certain personal information anytime you are in contact with Altayyaronline.com directly or indirectly through a third party. We will get any kind of personal information if you choose to give it to us in following circumstance: 

  * When you make a reservation or purchase any travel related products from our website or through our customer service team - by email, letter, fax, on the phone or in physical store 
  * When you register with us, subscribe to our newsletter, enter competitions / contest, send us queries or register for promotions 
  * When you take part in surveys or provide us with feedback 
  * When you engage with us in any online or offline event, promotions, page hosted by us on a third party platform or location 
  * When you engage with our affiliate partners, agents, channel sales /service partners, suppliers 

We may also collect and furnish such other information as is required in compliance of various laws, court order, as requested by other government or law enforcement authority, or in the good faith believe that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights or properties of Altayyaronline.com or any or all of its affiliates, associates, employees, directors or officers or when we have reason to believe that disclosing the information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference to our operations rights, interests, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities. 

### What is this information used for?

  * To conduct bookings, ticketing and payment transactions for the services available on the Site 
  * To personalize your experience and give you better service:  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 
  * To improve the user friendliness of the site;  
(we continually strive to improve the site offerings based on the information we receive from you 
  * To improve customer service   
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) 
  * Website traffic analysis 
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 
  * To send emails, SMS and other communications for providing services, responding to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions 
  * To respond to queries of the authorities in regard to your accessing of the site and services availed by you 
  * Automatic Logging of Session Data, IP and location information etc. 

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries or to our marketing partners or software Development partners. 

Of course, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords, and your Site membership account information. Please be very careful, responsible, and alert with this information, especially whenever you’re online. 

### Cookies and how do we use it?

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) to enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Yes, we use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and keep track of advertisements. This helps us to serve you better and more efficiently, and to personalize your experience at our Website. 

Similarly, a cookie may be placed by our third – party advertising companies or advertisement providers. These companies may use aggregated statistics about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide you advertisements about travel – related goods and services, your preferences in or any goods and services of potential interest to you. The third – party advertising companies or advertisement providers may also employ technology that is used to measure the effectiveness of our ads, your preference and other relevant statistical data to serve you better. Any such information may be anonymous about your visits to this and other sites and does not link online actions to an identifiable person. 

Mostly the Web browsers are programmed to automatically accept cookies but if you desire to opt from receiving the cookies you can do so by changing the options on your web browser or using certain software programs, you can control how and whether the cookies will be accepted by your browser. Altayyar does respects your right to block any unwanted Internet activity, especially that of unscrupulous websites, though blocking cookies from usage of Site may disable certain features on the Site, and may make it impossible to purchase or use certain services available on the Site. Please note that it is possible to block cookie activity from certain websites while permitting cookies from websites you trust, like altayyaronline.com Website. 

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. However, we do transmit your information to trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also the release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, other non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### Third party links

Altayyaronline Site contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are entering another website for which Altayyaronline has no responsibility and these third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies which you will have to acquaint yourselves with. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of all such sites as their policies may be materially different from our Privacy Policy. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### Contacting us

While using Altayyaronline.com, you consent to the collection and use of this information in the ways described above. If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, the practices of this site or your dealings with the site please email us to customerservice@altayyaronline.com and ibe.package@altayyargroup.com
